{
    "subject": "resource/Umayyad_Caliphate",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Dirham",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Umayyad Caliphate is Dirham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9407547116279602,
            "question": "Name the currency used during the Umayyad Caliphate."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9097683429718018,
            "question": "What was the currency of the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8821011185646057,
            "question": "Did the Umayyad Caliphate mint its own Dirhams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8496377468109131,
            "question": "Were there different types or denominations of Dirhams used by the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.689507782459259,
            "question": "Can we learn anything about the economy of the Umayyad Caliphate from its use of the Dirham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6326304078102112,
            "question": "What impact did the Dirham have on trade within the Umayyad Caliphate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5990986227989197,
            "question": "Was the Dirham a widely accepted currency in its time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44787004590034485,
            "question": "How was the Dirham valued compared to other currencies of the era?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4332847595214844,
            "question": "What type of unit was the Dirham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39114487171173096,
            "question": "Are there any historical records that mention the use of Dirhams?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Umayyad Caliphate is Dirham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8941_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of unit was the Dirham?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8941_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was the Dirham valued compared to other currencies of the era?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8941_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was the Dirham a widely accepted currency in its time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8941_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8941_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided contain information that supports the triple, including mentions of the dirham as a type of silver coin used throughout the different Caliphates of early Islam and its specific details such as composition, design, and minting location."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The documents provide information about the dirham, which was a type of silver coin used in the early Islamic Umayyad caliphate. This supports the statement that the currency of the Umayyad Caliphate was Dirham."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Dirham was a type of silver coin used throughout the different Caliphates of early Islam, but not all coins minted during the Umayyad Caliphate were dirhams. Other types of coins such as dinars and dirham-dinars were also minted during this period. Therefore, stating that the currency of the Umayyad Caliphate is only Dirham is incorrect.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text explicitly states that the dirham was a type of silver coin used throughout the different Caliphates of early Islam, and specifically mentions an Umayyad dirham minted in Iraq during the rule of the Umayyad Caliphate.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Umayyad Caliphate's official currency was the Dinar, not the Dirham.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context mentions that the dirham was a type of silver coin used throughout the different Caliphates of early Islam, including during the Umayyad Caliphate. Therefore, it is accurate to say that the currency of the Umayyad Caliphate included dirhams.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}